hi my name is Chris Haggerty I worked in
嗨，我叫克里斯·哈格蒂
a Java platform group at Oracle and
Oracle的Java平台小组和
today I'm going to give an introduction
今天我将作一个介绍
to the Java 11 HTTP client in this
到Java 11 HTTP客户端中
session we're going to take a look at
会议，我们将看一看
the main types of the API
API的主要类型
what module and package take me found in
在哪个模块和包装中找到我
had to perform some basic operations
必须执行一些基本操作
like sending a request and how response
例如发送请求以及如何响应
body is modeled enhancements in the JDK
主体是在JDK中建模的增强功能
are done through jdk enhancement
通过jdk增强来完成
proposals jeb 321 standardizes the API
建议jeb 321标准化API
that was incubating in previous JDK
在以前的JDK中孵化的
releases the HTTP client is provided by
释放HTTP客户端提供的
the Java net HTTP module and that module
Java net HTTP模块和该模块
exports a single package of the same
出口相同的单个包装
name unlike the previous incubating
名称与以前的孵化不同
version this module is now part of the
版本，此模块现在是
Java SE platform and as such is it is
Java SE平台本身就是这样
resolved by default when compiling a
编译时默认解决
running non modular code modular code
运行非模块化代码模块化代码
can in its module info source file need
可以在其模块信息源文件中需要
to require the Java net HTTP module
需要Java net HTTP模块
directly or required a Java SE
直接或需要Java SE
aggregator module the HTTP client class
聚合模块HTTP客户端类
is a top-level type an HTTP client can
是HTTP客户端可以使用的顶级类型
be used to send requests and retrieve
用于发送请求和检索
their responses HTTP client is created
他们的响应HTTP客户端被创建
to a builder the builder can be used to
对于建造者来说，建造者可以用来
complete their per client state like the
完成每个客户的状态，例如
preferred protocol version either HTTP 1
首选协议版本HTTP 1
1 or HTTP 2 whether to follow redirects
1还是HTTP 2是否遵循重定向
a proxy iConnect timeout and much more
代理iConnect超时等等
once built HTTP client is immutable and
一旦建立的HTTP客户端是不可变的，
can be used to send multiple requests
可用于发送多个请求
the HTTP client API follows the familiar
HTTP客户端API遵循熟悉的
builder pattern there are factories for
建设者模式有工厂
trading builders for the top-level HTTP
顶级HTTP的交易构建者
client and the HTTP request types in
客户端和HTTP请求类型
this example the HTTP client new builder
此示例HTTP客户端新构建器
static factory method returns a new
静态工厂方法返回新的
builder of HTTP client the prefer
HTTP客户端的构建者首选
protocol version HTTP to a set which is
协议版本HTTP到一组
the default the normal redirect policy
默认为正常重定向策略
is set which means to follow redirects
已设置，这意味着要遵循重定向
always unless been redirected from the
始终，除非已从
more secure HTTPS to the less secure
HTTPS越安全，安全性越差
HTTP the proxy of the given address
HTTP给定地址的代理
import has set a system-wide default
导入已设置系统范围的默认值
Authenticator is set in case the site
设置身份验证器以防站点
requires authentication a connects
需要验证连接
timeout for new connections is set to 20
新连接的超时设置为20
seconds and then the client is built
秒，然后建立客户端
multiple requests can be sent by a
一个请求可以发送多个请求
single client an HTTP request instance
单客户端HTTP请求实例
is built through a HTTP request builder
通过HTTP请求构建器构建
where the request URI can be set the
可以在其中设置请求URI的位置
request method the headers a body if any
请求方法，标头为正文（如果有）
and a request specific timeout once
和一次请求特定的超时
built a HTTP request is immutable
内置的HTTP请求是不可变的
similar to HTTP client the HTTP request
类似于HTTP客户端的HTTP请求
has a new builder factory method that
有一个新的生成器工厂方法
creates a new HTTP request builder that
创建一个新的HTTP请求构建器
builder can be used to set the prayer
建造者可以用来设定祈祷
request State in this example the
在此示例中的请求状态
request URI is set to open JDK dot
请求URI设置为打开JDK点
java.net a request specific time out of
java.net请求的特定时间超出
one minutes is set a header indicating
一分钟设置一个标题，指示
the content type since this will be a
内容类型，因为这将是
post request the body publishers of file
发布请求文件的正文发布者
factory method is used to return a
工厂方法用于返回一个
request body publisher that publishes
请求发布的正文发布者
the content of the given file path in
给定文件路径中的内容
this case in JSON requests are immutable
这种情况在JSON请求中是不可变的
and can be sent multiple times an HTTP
并可以通过HTTP多次发送
response is not created directly but
响应不是直接创建的，而是
rather returned as a result of sending
而是由于发送而返回
an HTTP request an HTTP response is made
一个HTTP请求一个HTTP响应
available when the response status code
响应状态代码可用
and headers have been received and
和头已收到和
typically after the response body has
通常在响应主体具有
also been completely received whether or
还是完全收到了
not the HTTP response is made available
没有HTTP响应可用
before the response body has been
在响应主体之前
completely received depends on the body
完全接受取决于身体
they're provided when sending the HTTP
发送HTTP时提供了它们
request they take a look at the buddy
要求他们看一下伙伴
handler more closely in a late later in
在晚些时候更紧密地处理
the presentation HTTP response provides
演示HTTP响应提供
methods for accessing to respond status
访问响应状态的方法
code the headers to response body and
将标头编码到响应主体并
the HTTP request corresponding to this
与此对应的HTTP请求
response the HTTP client supports
响应HTTP客户端支持
synchronous and asynchronous modes of
的同步和异步模式
operation requests sent with the
与一起发送的操作请求
synchronous send method blocked the
同步发送方法阻止了
current rate of execution until
直到当前执行率
responses available requests sent with
响应可用的请求发送
the send async method we turn a
发送异步方法，我们将
completable feature of HTTP response
HTTP响应的可完成功能
compatible future added in java 8
Java 8中添加了兼容的Future
provides a number of methods for
提供了多种方法
building chains of dependent actions
建立依存行为链
that can be run either synchronously or
可以同步运行或
asynchronously in this example the
在此示例中异步
clients send method is given the request
客户发送方法被给予要求
to be sent along with a body handler
与身体处理者一并发送
that converts the response body bytes to
将响应主体字节转换为
a string tenders bond status code and
字符串招标债券状态代码和
body are printed the send method blocks
正文打印发送方法块
the calling thread until the responses
调用线程直到响应
available this next example is the same
下一个示例可用的是相同的
code only written using the asynchronous
仅使用异步编写的代码
style the send async method is given a
样式发送异步方法被赋予
request to be sent and also a body
请求发送，还有一个尸体
hunter that converts the response body
转换响应主体的猎人
bytes to a string the completable
字节到可完成的字符串
theater then apply method is being used
剧院然后申请方法被使用
to create a dependent action the prints
创建打印的依赖动作
the response code and returns response
响应代码并返回响应
another down apply method is used to
另一种向下应用方法是
create another dependent action that
创建另一个依赖动作
map's the HTTP response to its body type
映射其主体类型的HTTP响应
which in this case is a string the den
在这种情况下是字符串den
accept method consumes that string and
accept方法使用该字符串，并且
just printed out Java util
刚刚打印出Java util
current flow was added in Java nine and
Java 9中添加了当前流程
it provides the reactive streams
它提供反应流
interfaces for the Java platform the
Java平台的接口
HTTP client models requests body using a
HTTP客户端模型使用
subtype of flow publisher a request body
流发布者的子类型请求主体
publisher the HTTP client subscribed to
HTTP客户端订阅的发布者
this publisher when sending a request
发送请求者时，此发布者
that has somebody on the receiving side
在接收方有人
when a response code and headers are
当响应代码和标题是
received the HTTP client calls the body
收到HTTP客户端调用的正文
handler the body hunter can then inspect
然后，身体猎人可以检查
the status code and headers if it wishes
状态码和标题（如果需要）
before creating a subscriber this
在创建订户之前
subscriber returned by the body hunter
身体猎人返回的订户
will be used to receive and process the
将用于接收和处理
actual response body bytes the HTTP body
实际响应主体字节，HTTP主体
subscriber
订户
is a subtype of flow subscriber and HTTP
是流订阅者和HTTP的子类型
client acts as a publisher of response
客户充当回应的发布者
body bytes looking a little closer at
身体字节看起来更近一点
the request body publisher it is a flow
请求主体发布者是流程
publisher of byte buffers the byte
字节的发布者缓冲字节
buffers contain the request body bytes
缓冲区包含请求主体字节
it also adds a single abstract method
它还添加了一个抽象方法
content length this method can
此方法可以的内容长度
optionally return the length of the
（可选）返回
request body if known a request body
请求体（如果知道）
publisher implementation is responsible
发布者的实施负责
for converting a high-level Java object
用于转换高级Java对象
like a string into a flow of byte
像一个字符串变成字节流
buffers that can then be sent as the
然后可以作为
request body the request body publishers
请求正文请求正文发布者
class contains only static methods and
类仅包含静态方法，并且
these methods are factories for creating
这些方法是用于创建的工厂
body publishers that can be used for
可以用于
most common use cases here we can see
我们可以在这里看到最常见的用例
some of the factories for curating a bud
一些用来策画芽的工厂
for creating body publishers from the
用于从
byte array or an interval of byte array
字节数组或字节数组的间隔
from a file path or a string as well as
从文件路径或字符串以及
from an input stream body Condor is a
来自输入流主体Condor是一个
functional interface that has a single
具有单个功能接口
method apply that takes a response info
应用方法以获取响应信息
containing the status code and headers
包含状态码和标题
the body handler is invoked when the
当
response status
回应状态
and headers are available but before the
和标头可用，但在
actual response body bytes have been
实际的响应主体字节为
received the body handler can inspect
收到身体处理者可以检查
there's response code and headers before
之前有响应代码和标头
returning the body subscriber that will
返回正文订阅者
then be used to receive the actual
然后用来接收实际
response body bytes body subscriber is a
响应正文字节正文订阅者是一个
flow subscriber of an aggregate of byte
字节流的流订阅者
buffers the byte buffers contain the
缓冲区字节缓冲区包含
response body bytes body subscriber adds
响应正文字节正文订阅者添加
a single abstract method get' body that
一个单一的抽象方法得到的身体
returns a completion stage that
返回完成阶段
completes with a higher-level type that
用更高级别的类型完成
the body subscriber implementation will
主体订户实施将
convert the response body bytes into in
将响应主体字节转换为in
many cases it is not necessary to deal
很多情况下没有必要处理
with body subscribers directly but
直接与主体订户联系，但
rather body hammer the body hung nerves
宁可全身锤击身体，垂下神经
class contains only static methods and
类仅包含静态方法，并且
these methods are frakked factories for
这些方法对于
creating body handlers that can be used
创建可以使用的身体处理程序
for both common news cases here we can
对于这两种常见新闻案例，我们可以
see some of the factories for creating
看到一些工厂创造
body hunters to convert the response
身体猎人转换反应
body into a byte array or a string to
正文转换为字节数组或字符串
stream it to a file or an input stream
将其流式传输到文件或输入流
as well as replacing and discarding
以及替换和丢弃
handlers when the actual response body
处理程序何时实际响应主体
is on an uninteresting and there are
没意思，有
more exotic handlers that act as
更多的异国处理程序充当
combiners and adapters for buffering and
组合器和适配器，用于缓冲和
interacting with regular flow
与常规流程互动
subscribers now let's take a look at
订阅者现在让我们来看看
some examples this is an example of a
一些例子，这是一个例子
synchronous get a new HTTP client is
同步获取一个新的HTTP客户端是
created over which the request will be
创建请求所依据的
sent a request is built with a given URI
发送的请求是使用给定的URI构建的
yet is the default method so there's no
仍然是默认方法，所以没有
need to explicitly set the method here
需要在这里明确设置方法
the clients ascend method is then called
然后调用客户端的升序方法
with the request the body handlers of
与请求的身体处理
string factory method returns a body
字符串工厂方法返回一个主体
handler that converts to response body
转换为响应主体的处理程序
bytes into a string the send method
字节转换为字符串的send方法
blocks until the response is completely
阻塞直到完全响应
received it then returns an HTTP
收到它然后返回一个HTTP
response of string
字符串的响应
they're sponsoring is then printed this
他们赞助，然后打印此
next example is similar to the previous
下一个示例与上一个类似
one only the code uses the asynchronous
一个只有代码使用异步
style the send async method is given a
样式发送异步方法被赋予
request to be sent and also a body
请求发送，还有一个尸体
handler converts response body bytes to
处理程序将响应正文字节转换为
a string the send async method returns a
发送异步方法返回的字符串
completable feature of HTTP response the
HTTP响应的可完成功能
completable future denn apply method is
将来可申请的报名方法是
used to create a dependent action that
用于创建一个依赖动作
map's the HTTP response to its body type
映射其主体类型的HTTP响应
which in this case in the string it is
在这种情况下，它在字符串中是
this dependent action that is then
然后是这种依赖动作
returned by the get edit there is no
由get edit返回，没有
code here that blocks callers of the get
此处的代码阻止了get的调用者
method can either create additional
方法可以创建其他
dependent actions chained off to return
依赖的动作被束缚起来以返回
computable future or called join to
可计算的未来或称为加入
explicitly block until the response body
明确阻止，直到响应主体
string is available moving to the next
字符串可移动到下一个
example again diskette method is similar
例子又是软盘方法类似
to that of the previous example only
仅与前面的示例相同
this time it rot writes the response
这次它烂了写响应
body to a file the body handlers of file
正文到文件的正文处理程序
factory method creates a body handler
工厂方法创建一个身体处理程序
that streams the response body to the
将响应主体发送到
given file path again this method is
再次给定文件路径，此方法是
asynchronous and note that none of the
异步，请注意，
code here blocks the returned
这里的代码阻止返回
completable future completes with the
可完成的未来与
file path when the response body has
响应主体具有的文件路径
been completely received and written to
已被完全接收并写入
the file next we have an example of a
接下来的文件我们有一个例子
post request this time the HTTP request
这次发布请求HTTP请求
builder has an explicit setter method
构建器具有显式的setter方法
called that sets post as the HTTP method
称为将post设置为HTTP方法的调用
the actual post method is given a body
实际的发布方法被赋予主体
publisher so that it knows how to get to
发布商，以便它知道如何到达
it to request body here the body
它要求身体在这里
publishers of string factory method is
字符串工厂的发布者方法是
used to create a body publisher that
用来创建一个正文发布者
publishes the given string the request
发布给定的字符串请求
is sent synchronously and this time
同步发送，这次
discarding body hunter discards response
丢弃尸体猎人丢弃响应
body
身体
HTTP responsive wild card which is an
HTTP响应通配符
unknown type this is a more advanced
未知类型，这是更高级的
example and demonstrates how to combine
示例并演示如何结合
Java streams and compatible future to
Java流和兼容的未来
send the number of requests and
发送请求数量并
collector responses they get your eyes
收集者的回应他们吸引了你
method takes a list of your eyes that
方法需要你的眼睛列表
will be retrieved this list of your eyes
将检索到您的此列表
is then converted into a list of HTTP
然后转换为HTTP列表
requests by stringing streaming over the
通过在
original list mapping each entry to a
将每个条目映射到一个原始列表
request builder and subsequently
请求建造者，随后
building the request and collecting to a
建立请求并收集到
new list next each request is sent
每个请求发送之后的新列表
asynchronously and the completable
异步且可完成
features of HTTP response are collected
收集HTTP响应的功能
into another list and that list is
进入另一个列表，该列表是
returned colors of the get your eyes
返回您的眼睛的颜色
method can inspect elements of the
方法可以检查元素
returned list to either chain dependent
返回列表到任一链依赖
actions or query for the completion to
动作或查询完成情况
summarize the standard HTTP client added
总结添加的标准HTTP客户端
in Java 11 is a replacement for
Java 11中的替代品
performing HTTP access to the URL
对URL执行HTTP访问
connection API which is now more than
连接API，现在已超过
twenty years old the HTTP client was
二十岁的HTTP客户
incubated in previous releases and
在以前的版本中孵育
standardized in Java eleven code using
Java 11代码标准化使用
the incubating version of the API will
API的孵化版本将
need to be updated for Java 11 minimally
最少需要为Java 11更新
the import statements will need to
导入声明将需要
reflect a new package name Java HTTP the
反映新的程序包名称Java HTTP
HTTP client API uses more modern
HTTP客户端API使用更现代
language features like generics and
语言特性，例如泛型和
lambda as well as more modern platform
lambda以及更现代的平台
API is like completable future and
API就像可以完成的未来，
reactive streams interfaces the API is
反应流接口的API是
deliberately small and compact you can
故意小巧紧凑
download Java 11 now at this URL please
请立即通过此URL下载Java 11
join us at open JDK or follow us on
加入我们的开放式JDK或关注我们
Twitter at open JDK or hashtag Java 11
公开JDK或Java 11主题标签上的Twitter
my own twitter handle is at checker
我自己的推特句柄在检查器上
$9.99
$ 9.99
Oracle is the steward of Java providing
Oracle是Java提供的管理员
a large amount of development
大量发展
engineering funding for the Java SE
Java SE的工程资金
platform and open JDK Oracle provides a
平台和开放的JDK Oracle提供了
leading class premier support for a low
一流的总理支持低
cost that's easy to purchase with simple
易于购买的成本
pricing tiers thank you for watching
定价层感谢您的观看
[Music]
[音乐]